真庆幸我们来了
I just love that we're here.
有什么比发展中国家获得清洁水资源
Is there anything more important than clean water
更重要的吗
in developing countries?
或者比一个干净的高脚杯更重要
Or a clean glass in this one?
是安妮·吉布斯 12频道的新闻女主播
It that Anne Gibbs, the lady from Channel 12 News?
天呐 那是安妮·吉布斯 我超爱她
Oh, my God! It's Anne Gibbs! Oh, I love her!
那要是安妮·海瑟薇
That reaction would've
这反应也太夸张了
been big if it was Anne Hathaway.
她坐在主播台后完全看不出身材这么好呢
Oh, she is hiding quite a figure behind that desk.
你跟安妮·吉布斯什么情况
Okay, what's going on with you and Anne Gibbs?
来吧 去跟她打个招呼
Come on. We gotta go say hi to her.
好吧 走吧
Okay, we're doing this.
抱歉打扰
I'm sorry.
我是你的粉丝
I am such a fan.
你做的那个驼背体操运动员的报道
I was so moved by that story you did
让我非常感动
about the gymnast with the hump.
-你知道不可思议的是什么吗 -什么
- You wanna hear something crazy? - Yeah.
他刚获得了圣母大学的奖学金
He just got a scholarship to Notre Dame.
不是吧 天呐
No! Oh, my gosh!
你可能经常听说这些事
You probably get this all the time,
但我也想跟你说个故事
but I have a story for you.
我代表一些无家可归的人士
I represent some homeless people
起诉一家剥削员工薪金的公司
in a case against a corporation that pays them slave wages.
-有意思 -是啊
- Interesting. - Yes.
这事有多长时间了
How long has this been going on?
从2012年开始的
Since 2012.
我们想让社会知道
We're just trying to shine a light
他们的处境有多糟
on how awful they're being.
非常糟糕
Truly awful.
你也在做这个吗
Are you working on this, too?
没有没有
Oh, gosh. No, no.
我是他的老公
I'm just this one's husband.
我是高中橄榄球队教练
I'm a high school football coach.
我叫卡梅隆·塔克
Cameron Tucker.
没错 老天 我好傻
Yes. Oh, god. I'm so embarrassed.
我叫米奇尔·普里契特 你好吗
Mitchell Pritchett. How are you?
-真的吗 -那么
- Really? - So --
你是个出柜的高中橄榄球教练吗
You are an openly gay high school football coach?
我懂我懂 你一听到橄榄球教练
I know, I know. You hear "football coach,"
就以为我会是
and you expect to meet somebody
像约翰·韦恩那样的硬汉吧[大喊"约翰·韦恩"]
that screams John Wayne.
但其实我唯一一次大喊"公爵"[约翰·韦恩的绰号]
Meanwhile, the only time I've screamed the duke
是那次我们争论《唐顿庄园》里谁最帅
is when we argue over who's the cutest on "Downton Abbey."
可怜的米奇尔 他听我喊了一百遍
Poor Mitchell. He's had to hear that a hundred times.
没错 没错
I have. I have.
那些流浪人员的时薪只有一美元
So these homeless people are making a dollar an hour --
现在出柜的橄榄球教练多吗
Are there a lot of openly gay coaches?
如果成人电影可信
Oh, if the adult film industry's to be believed,
那就到处都是
there all are.
这样做
It's in, you know,
明显违反了《联邦公平劳动标准法案》
clear violations Of the federal fair labor standards act --
有人联系你做新闻报道吗
Has anyone ever approached you for a news segment?
报道我吗 老天 没有 我觉得
On me?! Oh, my Gosh. No. I don't...
我觉得我的故事不足以做成
I don't think I'm interesting enough
一篇有意思的新闻报道
to do a news segment on.
记者要拿我说什么啊
I mean, what would a reporter even say about me?
说我是个拥有不败战绩
That I'm a high school football coach
勇于打破陈规的高中橄榄球教练吗
with an undefeated record who's tackling stereotypes?
说我带的队禁止偏见
That on my team, prejudice is considered out of bounds?
说我们突破偏执 摒弃狭隘
That we're blitzing bigotry, kicking intolerance,
-坚持不懈地... -使用比喻
- and beating... - metaphors to death?
你们想看点超酷的东西吗
You guys wanna see something really cool?
藏在那艘古老的船后面了吗
Is it behind that old boat?
这是有史以来最著名的战舰之一
This is one of the most famous warships of all time.
宪法号
The "U.S.S. Constitution."
服役84年
Stayed in active duty 84 years.
没有任何敌人成功登上这艘战舰
No enemy managed to board her.
才10秒 这船已经让我觉得无聊了
10 seconds, she's already bored me.
你的西语老师来了
That's your Spanish tutor.
我要再说一次
I'm gonna say it one more time.
我真的觉得法语更适合我
I really think French will be a better fit for me.
你的名字叫
Your name is
曼尼尔·阿尔伯特·哈维尔·亚历杭德罗·迪尔加多
Manuel Alberto Javier Alejandro Delgado.
法语怎么会更适合你
How is French a better fit for you?
我敢肯定
Okay, I'm pretty sure
你又加了个我从没听过的中间名
you threw in a name I've never heard before.
你好
Hello.
请说西语哦
AH, AH! En Espagnol, por favor.
行了 别要求这么高
Okay, let's take it down a nacho.
你好啊 迪亚高
Hola, Diego!
您一定是普里契特先生吧
You must be Mr. Pritchett.
叫我杰吧 很高兴你能来
Jay. And I'm just glad you're here.
歌洛莉亚试图教曼尼学西语
Gloria tried to tutor Manny.
《海伦·凯勒》那部电影里都没那么多叫喊场面
There was less yelling in "The Miracle Worker."
因为他连学都不学
Because he wasn't even trying.
抱歉 但对我来说
I'm sorry, but Spanish
西语听起来不太自然
just doesn't seem natural to me.
我不喜欢西语的发音方式
I don't like the way it hits my ear.
有什么能比你的母语听起来更自然的
What could be more natural than your mother's tongue in your ear?
你认不认识什么不错的英语老师
Do you happen to know a good English tutor?
亲爱的
Hey, honey!
还在准备考试吗
Still studying for that test?
不行 我要学习
I can't. I have to study.
你几点睡的
What time did you get to bed?
当然了
Sure thing.
克莱尔 我觉得艾丽克斯不太对劲
Claire, I think something's up with Alex.
不知道 某种鸡
I don't know. Some kind of chicken.
为什么没人听我说
Why is no one listening to me?
过来
Come here.
我觉得她睡眠不足
I don't think she's getting enough sleep.
你看她 简直像个自动吸尘器
Look at her. She's like a human roomba.
艾丽克斯没事
Alex will be fine.
这才是大问题
This is our real problem.
我今早去上班的时候
When I left for work this morning,
她就坐在沙发上翻杂志
she was sitting on the couch, flipping through magazines.
她20岁了 她在寻找自我
She's 20. She's finding herself.
那有多难啊 她连动都没动
How hard can it be? She hasn't moved.
那你20岁的时候在干什么
Well, what were you doing at 20?
我吗
Me?
我大学绩点4.0
I was getting a 4.0 in college.
我每周工作25小时
I was working 25 hours a week.
我在一个自杀热线当志愿者
I was volunteering at a suicide hotline.
别坐在沙发上了
Get off the couch!
做点什么改变你的生命吧
Do something with your life!
那是协助自杀热线吗
Was it an assisted suicide hotline?
你父亲回来了
Your father's home...
刚工作完
from work.
已经回来了吗 一定很棒
Already? Must be nice.
二爸 我的娃娃哭个不停
Daddy, my doll won't stop crying.
亲爱的 你试过关机吗
Oh, honey, did you try the "Off" switch?
我当然试过了
Of course I tried the "Off" switch!
莉莉
Lily!
抱歉我冲你吼了
Sorry I snapped.
但她已经哭了一整天了
She's been like this all d.
给你
There you go.
这招对你从不管用
That never worked on you.
好消息
So, good news.
安妮·吉布斯想要对我进行一个专题采访
Anne Gibbs actually wants to do a news segment on me!
什么
What?!
真是好消息 小卡
Great news, Cam.
太让人激动了
Isn't that exciting?
周五他们要派一个小组过来
They're gonna send a whole team Friday,
让摄影人员跟随录像
follow me around with a camera crew,
然后在主场比赛时采访我
then interview me at the homecoming games.
听着 我想请你帮我个大忙
So listen, I kinda have a big favor to ask.
好吧
Uh, w--okay.
依照传统 校队教练夫妇
Traditionally, the varsity coach and his wife
要在主场比赛前为整支球队
cook a big pancake breakfast
准备大型煎饼早餐会
for the football team for homecoming.
我有不祥的预感
I do not like where this is going.
先让我说完
Well, let me finish.
好吧 继续
Okay, continue.
我们一起
How would you feel
为学校橄榄球队准备煎饼早餐会
if you and I cooked a big pancake breakfast
你意下如何
for the varsity football team?
你说不说完有什么区别
Did you think that that was a twist?
米奇尔 拜托了
Mitchell, please.
不行
No!
除非你能说服汤姆·布拉迪来过夜
No, unless you can convince Tom Brady to spend the night,
不然我是不会给任何橄榄球员做早餐的
I am not making breakfast for any football players.
他是个橄榄球运动员对吧
He -- he is a football player, right?
是的 你引用的很正确
Yes. It's the perfect reference.
可米奇尔 这很重要
But, Mitchell, this is important.
我的工作也很重要 周五要做结案陈词
So is my job. I have closing arguments on Friday.
我保证你九点就可以走了
I promise you'll be out by 9:00.
我不过想向世界展示
I just wanna show the world
我们和异性恋夫妇一样
that we're as supportive and respectful
支持他人又值得尊重
as any straight couple.
你这话说得太世故了
That's an incredibly manipulative thing to say.
我不是那个意思
Well, that's not how I meant it.
你伤到我感情了
And that hurts my feelings.
天啊 你这一套好烂太容易被识破了
Oh, my God. This is so lame and transparent.
我认了 你比我聪明太多了
Busted. You know, you're so much smarter than me.
我真想知道如何把你这股兴奋劲关掉
Oh, I wish I knew where your "off" switch was.
你知道怎么把我的兴奋劲打开
Well, you know where my "on" switch is.
你好 邓菲女士 还记得我吗
Hey, Mrs. Dunphy. Remember me?
安迪 当然啦 进来吧
Andy. Of course. Come on in.
你是乔的保姆 对吧
You are Joe's babysitter, right?
在儿童保育界
Uh, "manny" is what we call ourselves
我们称自己为男保姆[曼尼]
in the child care community.
但在他们家叫这个有些乱
But it's confusing in that house
因为他们的儿子也叫曼尼
because of their son Manny.
所以我在试着改称"陪护哥"
So I've been trying to get traction with "bro-pair."
安迪你好
Hey, Andy.
你好 阁下 邓菲先生
Hey, Sir...uh, Mr. Dunphy.
抱歉 刚没看到你
Sorry. I didn't...see you.
安迪 邓菲阁下是我的英国名字
Andy, please. "Sir Mr. Dunphy" is my british name.
天啊 你即兴想出来的梗吗
Oh, my... you did not just think of that!
是啊
Yes!
安迪 你找我们有什么事
Andy, what can we do for ya?
我来这
I'm actually here --
安迪 你好
Hey, Andy.
来吧
Come on.
他是来找你的啊
He's here for you?
是的 我们要去地下室
Yeah. We're just gonna be in the basement.
见到你们很高兴
So good to see you guys.
我不知道我为什么要鞠躬
I don't know why I just did that.
什么情况
What was that?!
别生气
Don't be offended.
很多国家的文化习俗是只向男性鞠躬
In many cultures, it's customary to bow only to the man.
菲尔 海莉和安迪之间有情况吗
Phil. Haley, Andy -- is that a thing?
我不知道
Oh. I don't know.
希望没情况
Well, I hope not.
海莉处在人生的低谷
Haley is at a very low point in her life.
她现在最不需要的就是一段感情
It's the last thing she needs right now.
不觉得有时男生会是个好影响吗
Sometimes a boy might be a good distraction?
我还记得某位年轻小姐
I remember a certain young lady
玩"吃豆人"玩到上瘾
was pretty addicted to "Ms. Pac-man"
直到一位时髦的年轻男士引起了她的主意
until a dashing young gent caught her eye.
还不是因为你戴了个羽毛耳环
Only because you were wearing a feather earring.
那不是羽毛
It wasn't a feather.
是捕梦网
It was a dream catcher.
而且它起作用了
And it worked.
课上完了
Well, we're done.
这周再上一节
One more session this week,
曼尼就准备好考试了
and Manny will be ready for his test.
好的
Ay, qué bueno.
谢谢
Gracias!
他们在说什么
What are they saying?
我要是知道 还要他干啥
If I knew, he wouldn't be here.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我一个人在这做煎饼做了一小时
I've been cooking pancakes by myself for an hour.
有什么我能帮上忙的吗
What can I do to help?
你去打几个鸡蛋
Uh, you can crack some eggs over there.
说实话
You know what?
我觉得搅拌东西看起来好些
I think whisking might read better.
你干什么呢 盆里什么都没有
What are you doing? There's nothing in there.
唐 你能看出来这里没东西吗
Don, can you tell there's nothing in here?
不能
All good.
唐说没事
Don's all good.
我们还要去拍点别的东西
So we're getting some extra footage.
行话叫"幕后花絮"
What we call "b-roll."
安妮想拍我帮忙做饭的镜头
Anne wants to see me help cook.
我想让你帮忙做饭
I wanna see you help cook.
我还以为这是我们两个共同完成的呢
I thought this was something that we were doing together.
你说得对 一起来吧 抱歉
Yes, you're right. Okay, let's do this. Sorry.
完美 我很满意
That's perfect. I'm happy.
唐很满意
Don's happy.
我不满意
I'm not happy.
伙计们 吃得如何
What's up, guys!?
普里契特先生
Ah, Senor Pritchett.
一起来吧
Please, join us.
感谢你请我到我自家的泳池游泳
Nice as it is for you to invite me to swim in my own pool,
我还以为请你来是给曼尼教西班牙语的
I thought I was paying you to teach Manny Spanish.
曼尼上完课了
Manny's done with his lesson.
但迪亚高还是个游泳教练
But Diego here is also a swim instructor,
他要教乔游泳
So he's going to teach Joe to swim.
他水平一定很高
Must be a good teacher
乔不用在场都能学会
if Joe doesn't have to be here for it.
曼尼在给他换游泳尿布
Manny's putting him in his swimming diaper.
他们来了
There they are!
我们游泳吧
Let's go swim!
到我这来
Come here.
知道吗 自从你给我们看了那个模型
You know, after you showed us that cool model,
我就开始仔细研究"美国宪法号"
I started reading up on the "U.S.S. Constitution."
这船在那个年代可真具规模
Quite a ship in its day.
当然后来人们造了蒸汽船
En, of course you invented steam ships.
你这个老帆船护卫舰是无法
Your old sailing frigates just couldn't compete
和那些又新又快的
with those younger, faster,
蒸汽船模型抗衡的
steamier models in the water.
真是太遗憾了
You know, it's too bad
你不好好做西班牙语作业
you don't spend as much time
却花大把时间上网
on your spanish homework as you do online
千方百计寻找
finding passive-aggressive ways
攻击我的兴趣爱好的方法
of using my hobbies against me.
这是什么
What's this?
家长批准函
Permission slip.
让我转学法语
Lets me transfer into French.
只需一位家长签字即可
Only one parent signature required.
求你了 杰 我受不了了 我放弃
Come on, Jay. I can't take it anymore. I quit.
你听起来已经像个法国人了
You're already starting to sound French.
亲爱的 我开始担心艾丽克斯了
Honey, I'm getting worried about Alex.
我觉得她昨晚又没睡觉
I don't think she slept again last night.
已经连续三个晚上了
It's like the third night in a row.
我以为你会定闹钟起来看看她的
I thought you were gonna set your alarm and check on her?
可是那破玩意根本没响
Stupid thing never went off.
我敢肯定艾丽克斯睡觉了
I'm sure Alex slept.
我不知道
I don't know.
她坐在桌子前 眼珠都懒得动一下
She's sitting at her desk, too tired to move her eyeballs.
她是这样拿着书在看的
She's reading her book like this.
谁看见我的豹纹裙子了
Did anyone see my leopard print skirt?
我在楼梯上看见一条豹纹头巾
I saw a leopard headband on the stairs.
那就是了
That's it.
艾丽克斯没事
Alex is gonna be fine.
这位才是我所担心的
That's the one I'm worried about.
我要去跟她谈一谈
I'm gonna go talk to her.
真不敢相信我把她的裙子套在头上
I can't believe I just went power-walking
出去锻炼了
with her skirt on my head.
海莉 亲爱的 我想跟你谈谈
Haley, honey, I wanted to talk to you
关于你和安迪的事
about this whole thing with Andy.
有什么可谈的
What's there to talk about?
我担心那会使你分心
Well, I'm concerned that it is distracting you
无暇去做真正重要的事
from what's really important.
妈妈 你完全没必要担心
Oh, mom, there's nothing to worry about.
我们只是肉体关系
You know, it's just sex.
什么
What?
纯肉体的 只是释放压力的途径而已
Purely physical. It's really just a stress-reliever.
我根本没跟安迪上床 我们只是朋友
I am not having sex with Andy. We're just friends.
我在帮他准备工作面试
I'm helping him prep for a job interview
这件事他不希望别人知道
that he doesn't want anybody to know about.
用上床这个借口
The whole sex thing was the fastest way
是堵住我妈妈嘴的最快方法
to end the conversation with my mother.
还有别的问题吗
Uh, are there any more questions?
-没了 -好的
- No. - Okay, cool.
是他来了
Oh, that's him.
你看起来真帅啊
Hey! Oh, you look so good!
快进来 准备好了吗
Come inside. Are you ready?
是的 我在网上看了些东西
Yeah. I saw some stuff online,
有些新花样我想试试
so I got a couple new things I wanna try out.
来吧
Let's do it!
这就证明 安妮
...which proves, Anne,
同志教练也能带出好队伍
you can score with a gay coach.
等等 能不能重来一遍
Wait. Uh, can I try that again?
不用 刚才很好
No, that was great.
你的另一半是怎么看待你做教练这件事的
Um, how does your spouse feel about you coaching?
他吗
Oh, this one?
他是我的动力 他是...
He's my rock. He's...
他就是我的康妮·布里登
He's my Connie Britton.
你的 你的康妮·布里登
Your...your Connie Britton?
是《胜利之光》里的教练夫人
Mrs. Coach on "Friday Night Lights."
我能跟你聊几句吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
唐 安妮 我们能不能
Uh, Don, Anne? Can we, uh...
当然可以
Sure.
怎么了
Yeah, what's up?
你有没有意识到
Do you have any idea
这一上午你是怎么侮辱我的
how insulting you've been to me all morning?
就因为我把你比作康妮·布里登吗
What, because I just compared you to Connie Britton?
米奇尔 她跟泰勒教练是平等的
Mitchell, she was an equal to coach Taylor.
你看过那部剧的话就知道了
You'd know that if you saw the show.
我猜我没看过的原因就是
Well, I guess I missed it
《小卡秀》总是没完没了地在播
because "The Cam show" was always on.
真的吗 你就那么不想让我出出风头吗
Really? You're not gonna let me have my moment here?
你总是在出风头
It is always your moment,
通常我是不在意的
and usually I-I'm fine with that.
但是那天晚上
But the other night,
我试图让他们来报道我的案子
I was trying to get them to cover my case,
而你 你却非要抢风头
and you -- you made it all about you.
我没有 你这样说不公平
I did not. That is unfair.
我一直都支持你的工作
I have always supported your job
我知道你的工作有多重要
and know how important it is.
是吗 我的新案子是什么
Really? What's my new case about?
这三周来我一直在跟你说这一个案子
The only one I was talking about for three weeks.
有人
People...
需要他人支持
who need people.
他们幸运吗 小卡
Are they lucky, Cam?
他们是这世上最幸运的人吗
Are they the luckiest people in the world?
二爸 她又开始哭个不停了
Daddy, she won't stop crying again.
等一下 宝贝
One second, honey.
小卡 我很爱你
Look, Cam, I love you very much,
但我不喜欢你今天对待我的态度
but I resent the way you're treating me today.
好吗 我不是什么50年代的家庭主妇
Okay, I am not some 1950s housewife. I...
你是不是签了什么东西
Did you sign something
同意让曼尼改学法语
so that Manny could switch to French?
是的
I did.
你知道我希望他学西班牙语的
You knew that I wanted him to learn Spanish.
我也知道你不能强迫孩子
I also know you can't force a kid
去喜欢自己不感兴趣的东西
to be interested in something that he's not.
所以我才有一张
That's why I have a picture
米奇尔和他的舞伴握手的照片
of Mitchell and his prom date shaking hands.
要是你们能在意一下
It would be nice for someone to care
我的感受就好了
what I think for a change.
还有件事 我请了个新的游泳教练
You should also know that I hired a new swimming instructor.
不过别担心
But don't worry.
她也有宽阔的肩膀和小胡子
She's got the same broad shoulders plus a mustache.
这些都是因为你嫉妒吗
So all this is because you're jealous?
真不敢相信你居然这么...
I can't believe that you're being so...
自...
in...fer...ur--
那个词是什么来着
What is the word?
-自私 顽固 -真的吗
- Selfish. Pigheaded. - Really?
她说的 不是我
Her words, not mine.
你知不知道说每句话之前都要
Do you know how frustrating it is
别人当着面笑话我
To have people laugh in my face
就因为我想不出来某个词
because I'm struggling to find the words?
你应该穿我的鞋说一段
You should try talking in my shoes for one mile!
我想你的意思是
I think you meant --
我知道我的意思是什么
I know what I meant to mean.
你知道我说西语的时候有多睿智吗
Do you even know how smart I am in Spanish?
你当然不知道
Of course you don't.
哪怕只有一次 我想在自己家里
For once, it would be nice to speak to someone
讲一回自己的语言
in my own language in my own home.
不管用西语该怎么说
Whatever the Spanish word
但你想说的也是"女人呐"对吧
is for "women," Am I right?
-我的妈呀 -天啊
- Mother nature! - Cheez-its!
安迪 我不知道你在那里
Andy. I did not know you were there.
抱歉 我走路声音太小了
Sorry. Stupid little cat feet.
我不知道海莉在哪
I'm not sure where Haley is.
其实 邓菲先生 我有话想跟您说
Actually, Mr. Dunphy, I was hoping I could speak with you.
是吗 我有什么能帮你的
Oh, yeah? What can I do for ya?
邓菲先生
Mr. Dunphy,
我喜欢当男保姆
I love being a manny,
但我不可能永远做这个
but I can't do it forever.
我只是不知道下一步该怎么走
I just didn't know what the next chapter should be,
直到我遇见了一个叫菲尔·邓菲的人
but then I met a guy named Phil Dunphy.
-是吗 -他热爱自己的事业
- What? - A guy who loves what he does, and...
他为自己的家庭提供了这么好的条件
Yeah. A guy who provided all this for his family.
于是我意识到
And then I realized,
我想要投身房地产业
a career in real estate is what I want.
我希望自己能够
And I was hoping I could...
向最优秀的人学习
learn from the best.
斯基普·乌斯纳姆吗
Skip woosnum?
我可以帮你打个电话
Um, I can put in a call.
-他一般不回电话 -不
- He doesn't really get back -- - No.
是你
You.
安迪 我受宠若惊
Andy, I'm -- I'm so flattered.
我
I'm, uh,
可我现在不需要助手
I'm just not in the market for an assistant right now.
是啊
Yeah.
是我太蠢了 居然跑来这样问你
Stupid. That was stupid to even ask.
很感谢你花时间听我说
Thank you so much for your time.
第一课 永远不要接受"不"这个答案
Lesson number one -- never take "No" for an answer!
向我推销你自己
Now make me buy you.
好吧
Okay.
我很努力工作 我很爱干净
Uh, I'm a hard worker, I am very clean,
我很殷勤
I am eager to please,
我上厕所超快
I take super quick bathroom breaks,
而且我永远也不会
and I will never, ever...
我词穷了
Oh! I'm blanking on the verb!
要停止做某事怎么说来着
W-uh... when you give up on something?
半途而废
Quit?
我必须要问你
I had to ask
是因为我根本不知道那个词的意思
because I don't know the meaning of the word.
太棒了
Nice!
这里什么情况
What's going on here?
介绍一下我的新助手
I'm introducing you to my new assistant.
我的肋骨
Oh, my ribs!
邓菲先生 太感谢你了
Mr. Dunphy, thank you so much.
我不会让你失望的
I will not disappoint you.
安迪 你觉得这是个好主意吗
Andy, do you think this is a great idea,
毕竟你和海莉在...
considering that you and Haley are...
你知道的
You know.
做那种事
Doing it.
-我的妈呀 -天啊
- Mother nature! - Cheez-its!
不 我们只是互相帮助
No.We were just helping each other
准备工作面试
get ready for job interviews.
我和您女儿之间没有任何
There is nothing inappropriate happening
不正当关系
between me and your daughter.
海莉要去参加面试吗
Haley has a job interview?
她正在面着呢
That's where she is right now.
跟谁面试
With who?
加文·辛克莱
Gavin Sinclair.
超有名的明星造型师
The big-time stylist to the stars?
就是掌掴了播报员凯蒂·库瑞克的那个人
He's the one that slapped Katie Couric.
我们的小女孩终于长大了
Our little girl's gonna be okay after all!
我怎么跟你说的
All right! What'd I tell ya?
我们的女儿是个斗士
One thing about our girl -- she's a fighter.
你好 我跟加文·辛克莱有约
Hello. I have an appointment to see Gavin Sinclair.
今天不行 他大姨夫来了
Not today. He's in a mood.
好哒
'kay!
煎饼早餐会之后我感觉很不好
I felt awful after that pancake breakfast,
不只是因为米奇尔没把培根煎熟
and not just because Mitchell undercooked the bacon.
我不喜欢自己对他的案子一无所知
I hated that I didn't know what his case was about.
所以我去比赛的路上顺道去了法庭
So I popped by the courtroom on the way to the game.
这些人靠吸穷人的血为生
These people preyed on the poorest members of society --
那些没有能力自我辩护的人
Those who are unable to defend themselves.
他们不受尊重
They were treated with disrespect.
他太棒了
He was amazing!
他做这一切都不是为了他自己
And he wasn't doing any of it for himself.
他在帮助那些需要帮助的人
He was just trying to help those in need.
你能想象自己被剥夺了最基本的权利以及
Can you imagine being robbed of your basic rights
用于糊口的工资吗
and a living wage?
这么多年来米奇尔总是全力支持我
And after all those years of Mitchell supporting me,
我很高兴看到他成为人群焦点
I was so happy to see all eyes on him.
这是属于他的时刻
It was his moment.
这是如此不公
It's unfathomable.
而这个案子...
But what this case...
正如我所说
As I was saying,
这个案子事关尊严
what this case is about is dignity --
那些尊严...
the dignity of those...
我们需要接纳这些人
And we need to take these people
偿还他们
and we need to get them back...
很抱歉我没跟你说就让曼尼
Listen, I'm sorry I let Manny switch over to French
去学法语了
without consulting you.
我没有考虑过你一直得说英文
I didn't think how it must be for you
是种什么感受
having to speak English all the time.
你根本不懂
You have no idea.
我只是想告诉你我把家教请回来了
Anyway, I just wanted to tell you I hired the tutor back.
曼尼会不高兴的
Manny's not gonna like that.
他太沉迷于法语了
He's too much into his French thing.
家教不是给曼尼请的 是给我自己
The tutor's not for Manny. It's for me.
杰 我好开心
Ay, Jay, I love it!
现在换你听起来傻乎乎的了
Now you sound like the stupid one!
是我 我回来了
It's me. I'm back.
为什么
Why?
我跟一个朋友约好了
I made a pact with a friend of mine,
不见到加文·辛克莱
and I am not leaving this office
我就不走了
until I meet with Gavin Sinclair.
我不管你有多么宏伟的梦想
I don't care what's on your vision board.
你不能进去
You're not getting in there.
所以请你...
So if you could just...
我要忙疯了
I'm insanely busy.
妮基 谢天谢地你在这
Nikki, thank God you're here.
帮我剥橙子皮
Peel this orange for me.
辛克莱先生 我是海莉·邓菲
Mr. Sinclair, it's Haley Dunphy.
我是来面试助手职位的
I was supposed to see you for the assistant job.
我学习了您的作品
I have been studying your work,
不得不说
and I have to say
你为纽约时装周设计的作品
the looks that you did for New York fashion week
-让您... -我现在太忙了
- put you -- - Ah! I'm really too busy right now.
但我大老远开过来
But I drove all the way down here.
我们约好了的
We had an appointment!
是没错 但我查看了你的博客
Yeah, I looked at your blog.
对我来说有点太故意卖萌了
It's a little too cutesy for me.
我需要一个犀利的人
I need someone with edge.
我很犀利啊
I have edge.
你真没有那种劲儿
You really don't.
你是我见过的眼睛最大的人[天真无知]
You are literally the most wide-eyed person I've ever seen.
你的脸跟卡通小羊羔形象一样
You have the face of a cartoon lamb.
不过还是谢谢你能过来一趟
Thanks for coming by, though.
那是什么玩意儿 我想要的是皮
What is that? I wanted the peel.
我觉得你不喜欢卖萌这点真的很奇怪
I think it's weird you don't like cutesy
因为你旗下一半出席格莱美奖的客户
Considering half your clients at the grammys looked like
看上去像是刚从我的幼稚痴梦里走出来的
they just stepped out of a my little pony fever dream.
说得好 但不准抨击我
That's good. But not at me.
永远不准抨击我
Never at me.
妮基 站住
Nikki, stop.
妮基的服饰有5处明显的不当
There are five things wrong with Nikki's outfit.
请问分别是什么
What are they?
她就站在那儿呢
Uh, she's standing right there.
我可比她打扮得好多了
I'm dressed better than she is.
那件背心让你显得像是"独乳兽"
The tank gives you a uniboob.
你的手表太大了
The watch is too big.
哈伦裤 坡跟靴 别逗了
The harem pants, the wedge boots,
那皮带是要闹哪样
and come on, that belt?
90年代风情都已经过时3年了
The '90s have been out for three years.
已经5处了
And that's five.
需要我来点评一下你吗
Now should I do you?
胜利 太漂亮啦[法语]
Victoire! C'est magnifique!
打扰一下 小少年
Uh, excuse me, young man.
是塔克教练公开性取向
Was it coach Tucker's openness
给了你出柜的勇气吗
that gave you the courage to come out?
什么
What?
-你也来啦 -过来
- Hey, you! - Come here.
法院那边耽搁了一下
Court ran a little late,
但我还是看到你们获胜了
but I got to see you win.
-恭喜啊 -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you!
你是化妆了吗
Are you wearing makeup?
就脸上抹了一点
Oh, well, just on my face
以及耳朵 脖子和手 没错
And my ears and my neck and my hands, yeah.
听着 关于今天早上的事...
Okay, so listen. About this morning --
塔克教练 塔克教练
Uh, coach Tucker, coach Tucker.
能请你就这次的大胜利发表一下感言吗
Can we get a few words on your big win?
我得 接受一下采访
Oh, um, I-I need to do this.
好的 当然了 没事
Yeah. Of course you do. Yeah, it's fine.
跟我说说 教练
So tell me, coach,
这次胜利是什么感觉
how does this victory feel?
感觉棒极了
Well, it feels great.
显然 我感觉就像橄榄球女王一样
Obviously, I feel like the belle of the football.
唐喜欢这个笑话 唐在笑呢
Don liked that one. Don's laughing.
我很感激学校的支持
Well, I'm grateful to this school, you know,
以及孩子们和家长们
and the kids and the parents.
但是 我必须说 我最感激的...
But, um, you know, I gotta say, I'm most grateful for --
是这边这位 也就是我丈夫
for this guy right here, my husband.
米奇尔 米奇尔·普里契特
Uh, Mitchell. Mitchell Pritchett.
他是个律师
He's an attorney
专为那些默默无闻的弱势群体发声
who is the voice for people without one.
他是个真英雄
He is a-a real hero...
但却没有受到应得的赞美和赏识
who doesn't get the credit he deserves.
今天 我特意赶去法庭欣赏他的雄姿
Today, I went down and I watched him in the courtroom.
我就知道那人是你
I knew that was you.
我听出你的手机铃声了
I recognized your ringtone.
我正在蓄势待发呢
I'm building to something.
虽然 我获得了很多关注
You know, yeah, I get a lot of attention,
就是 指导这次比赛
you know, coaching this game.
但站在我身边的这位男人
But this man right here
默默地维护着
quietly defends the rights
那些困难群体的权利
of real people with real problems.
无家可归的人 被迫去找工作
Homeless people forced to get jobs.
不 不是这么回事
No, that's not it.
就相差那么一点点了
That's not it, but it was so close.
是的 我站在这里
Yes, I am standing here
勇敢地废止人们对同性恋的固有印象
boldly abolishing gay stereotypes.
但是...
But...
我的妆都花了 对吧
My makeup's running, isn't it?
我做到了 我得到那份工作了
I did it! I got the job!
真的吗
Really?
-亲爱的 我好为你骄傲 -谢谢
- Honey, I'm so proud! - Thank you!
我从未怀疑过你
Never doubted you.
太棒了 太棒了
So great. So great.
亲爱的
Sweetheart!
是啊 整个过程 跟坐过山车一样跌宕起伏
I know! It was such a roller coaster!
那个前台接待太刻薄了
The receptionist was so mean,
我就躲在车里哭了一阵
and I went and I cried in my car.
我当时都打算离开了
And I was about to leave,
但我突然想起来
but I remembered
你跟我爸谈的时候有多勇敢
how brave you were talking to my dad,
所以我又重新走进去了
so I got back in there!
我也按照你说的坚持忍住了没吐
And I did that thing you said about not throwing up.
天啊
Oh, my god.
我看某些男孩真的是有积极影响力的
I guess some boys are a good distraction.
是啊 他正是她现在所需要的
Yeah, he could be exactly what she needs right now.
我不知道你是怎么看的
And I don't know about you,
但我感觉到他们之间有点小火花
but I'm sensing a little heat over here.
天啊 我真为你高兴
Oh, my god! I'm so happy for you!
真的太棒了
Oh, this is so great.
谢谢你 邓菲先生
And thanks to you, Mr. Dunphy,
我终于可以省钱为贝丝买订婚戒指了
I can finally save up and get Beth that engagement ring.
贝丝是谁
Who's Beth?
他女朋友
His girlfriend.
所以你们两个并没有在一起吗
So you two really aren't together?
-没有 -没有
- No. - No.
她真的好痴迷于我们是一对啊
She's, like, really obsessed with us.
克莱尔
Claire?
书上的文字都好像在震动一样
The words on the page are vibrating,
我无法让它们停下来
and I can't make them stop.
我不知道怎么看书了
I forgot how to read!
艾丽克斯 天啊
Alex, oh, my god.
读给我听吧 妈咪
Read it to me, mommy?
宝贝 你精疲力尽了
Baby, you're exhausted
你得立刻去睡觉
and you need to go to sleep right now.
跟我来 跟我来
Come with me. Come with me.
好吧 你的一切看法都是错的
Yes, you were wrong about everything!
"好哒"
"'kay"?
谁会说"好哒"啊
Who says "'kay"?!
你真是蠢得要死
You're so stupid!
走开 绕过去
Go! Go around!